{
    "subject": "resource/Shahid_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Prabhleen_Sandhu",
    "human_readable": "The film Shahid features Prabhleen Sandhu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9373465776443481,
            "question": "What role does Prabhleen Sandhu play in Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8992230296134949,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Prabhleen Sandhu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7648612260818481,
            "question": "Who directed the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.727513313293457,
            "question": "Are there other actors besides Prabhleen Sandhu in Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644352912902832,
            "question": "What genre is the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.63521409034729,
            "question": "Is Prabhleen Sandhu an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6292478442192078,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5813286304473877,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5546838641166687,
            "question": "Where was the film Shahid filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45489591360092163,
            "question": "When was the film Shahid released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Shahid features Prabhleen Sandhu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2646_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Shahid filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2646_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who stars in the film Shahid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2646_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of the film Shahid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2646_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2646_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which explicitly mention that Prabhleen Sandhu stars in the film \"Shahid.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}